It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's a family guy
We now return to Julia
Louis-Dreyfus in Now It's Just Getting Sad.
Okay, okay, hear me out.
My character is a therapist
living in the city,
but I'm married to an elephant.
Hi, I'm the husband.
Hey, honey. We're going to my parents'
this weekend. Did you pack your trunk?
I don't think I want to go.
- I don't like going to your parents'.
- Why?
Maybe because
your dad's an ivory hunter?
- See? There's a lot going on here.
- Lot going on.
It actually...
It actually gets pretty watchable.
Damn, it's still raining.
Lois, you mind if I go in the house?
Fine, fine, just put the newspaper down.
Hey, Lois, look at this. The church
is holding auditions for a new organist.
Really? Wow. You know,
that sounds like it could be a lot of fun.
Yeah, it's been a while since
you've had the chance to play in public.
Church organist? That's boring.
Why don't you do something
more interesting?
Like when I had that job
feeding the homeless.
That's gonna make you big and strong.
Burping time.
Smells like someone needs to be changed.
When was the last time
you were changed? Seven days ago?
That's one week.
There are seven days in a week.
I love you, filthy hobo.
All right.
Why do you say "organist"
if you don't want...
I don't understand the world anymore.
Here be a jaunty sea shanty
from me boyhood.
You shake me nerves
and you rattle me brain
Too much love drives a man insane
You broke me will
Oh, what a thrill
Goodness gracious, great balls of fire
I know what boys like
I know what guys want
Boys like
Boys like me
All right, up next is Lois Griffin.
Well, I don't know if I can compete with
the rest of these people, but here goes.
My word, what a fascinating man
this Jesus must've been.
I can just imagine meeting him.
That was beautiful, Mrs. Griffin.
Up next is, Jake Tucker.
Finally. Some of us
have been waiting all evening
for a certain wife to come home
and feed her starving family.
Peter, I told you I was gonna be late.
Couldn't you have handled dinner?
You can't ask me to make dinner, Lois.
That's like asking me to choose between
Sarah Jessica Parker and Kirsten Dunst
in a hot body /weird face contest.
- It can't be done.
- Well, I've got good news.
I'm gonna be the church's new organist.
- Hey, congrats.
- Wow, Mom, that's great.
That means you'll play the organ.
It also means that this family is gonna
start going to church again on Sundays.
Being there today reminded me
of how important religious services are
to the moral fiber of a family.
And lately this family has been lacking
moral fiber. Especially you, Meg.
Meg! What happened to you?
She can't answer you. She can't even talk.
Ever since she started smoking pot,
she just kind of lays there.
It's really sad and a tiny bit funny.
Oh, my God,
I think I'm getting a contact high.
Now I'm messed up, too.
Good morning, everyone.
Please turn to hymn number 387.
God, you are so cool
Although, sometimes
it's, like, what's the deal?
You never answer your cell phone
And your messages are often ambiguous
Amen
A reading from the book of Leviticus.
"Thou shalt not spill thy seed
into thy sock,
"and then cram it
to the bottom of the hamper
"like it's been there a long time. "
The word of the Lord.
- Praise be to God.
Oh, I am so hungry. Hey, look,
they're handing out cookies up there.
Stewie, wait, don't...
Hey, there. Eat up, y'all.
Youse is good churchgoing folk.
Y'all deserve a little treat.
Give me that!
Well, aren't you
an enthusiastic wafer muncher.
What is that, punch?
Oh, don't y'all drink that.
Youse gonna get sick.
Yup.
- That baby just threw up the host!
- That's a sign of the devil!
- Oh, my God, is he possessed?
- He's possessed!
That baby is possessed by Satan!
Calm down, everyone.
He's just a little sick.
I'll take him home. Come on, sweetie.
Sweet, we are out of here. Now I can do
what I planned to do this morning.
Gladiator mice.
Yes! Yes! Die! Die! Die!
I have everything and you have nothing!
What a horrible morning.
You know, all I wanted
was for us to share a simple
Sunday church service as a family.
But I guess that's too much to ask.
Good afternoon, Mrs. Griffin.
We're here to take custody of your baby
so that the good reverend here
can perform an exorcism
and banish the devil from his infant soul.
What? You are not performing
an exorcism on my baby.
Mrs. Griffin, you can give him to us,
or we can take him by force.
- No!
- Don't worry, Lois.
We'll hide in the one place
they can't find us.
In imagination land.
Where you burp where you fart
and you fart where you burp.
Indeed, that's how it happens.
Where're we going?
Who cares? As long as it's away
from those bloody church fanatics.
We're going to Texas. We can stay at my
sister Carol's place until this blows over.
Texas? We're going to Texas
in search of religious tolerance?
That's gonna be like trying to get
Sneakers O'Toole to take his sneakers off.
I'm not taking my sneakers off
I'm Sneakers O'Toole
Hey, take those sneakers off.
- No!
- Take them off, I said!
No!
Let him go. We'll never catch him.
Not in these shoes.
I didn't take my sneakers off
I'm still Sneakers O'Toole
Holy crap!
You marry Billy Joel,
it's gonna happen one way or another.
- Good evening. I'm Tom Tucker.
- And I'm Diane Simmons.
Authorities are on the lookout
for one-year-old Stewie Griffin,
a Quahog infant who is believed
to be possessed by Satan.
A substantial reward is being offered for
any information leading to his capture.
In other pseudo-scientific news, a local
man claims to have spotted Bigfoot.
We've got the exclusive interview.
I was about to bone my girlfriend,
out at the lake,
but suddenly, she yelled,
so I looked up and it was Bigfoot.
- So, what happened next?
- Then, I went back to bone her,
but the mosquitoes were going crazy
and she said there was no way.
All right, get your snacks,
and hurry out, you guys.
There, look, they have Chunky bars.
What a God-awful mess those things are.
Chocolate with raisins in it.
Yeah. Yeah, that's what kids
want with their chocolate, fruit.
Why don't you put sunflower seeds
in the Ding Dongs while you're at it?
Is that part of your stand-up act?
- I don't know. Did you like it?
- I wouldn't open with it.
Pardon me, sir.
We're trying to locate a possessed child.
Have you seen anyone who looks like this?
Yeah, that's my son.
He's actually in the Mini Mart right now.
He'll be out in a second.
I mean, I mean, no.
No, never seen him before.
Hmm...
What was that first thing you said?
Oh, I was just saying
that baby in the picture is my son.
He's traveling with us.
He's part of our family.
We're trying to avoid being found
by police like you.
I mean, I was just remarking
what a nice tie you have on.
I love this tie.
All right, you folks take care now.
Did you hear that cashier's accent?
" Would you like
some change please, for you?"
You know, if it weren't for 9/11,
those guys would be adorable.
Oh, my God, look!
Quick, into the bathroom!
We're gonna have to come up with a way
to change your appearance.
Well, I could disguise myself
as Britney Spears.
I'm already standing in urine,
and I hate the person I'm with.
Now, let's see, there's got to be
something in here we can use.
Boy, that was a close one back there.
Way to think on your feet, Brian.
Well, we got lucky.
How you holding up, Stewie?
Um...
I feel right, Brian. I feel right.
Are you sure Aunt Carol won't mind
us using her house?
She won't care, Chris.
She's off on her ninth honeymoon.
When will it work for her?
Howdy, new neighbors.
Pleased to welcome you.
We're the Lynches. We live next door.
Nice to meet you. We're the Griffins.
Nellie here is a homemaker,
and I'm a queer chaser and beater.
Lois, I'm not sure
this is the right place for us.
These Texans are socially backward and
politically, they're all stubborn as a mule.
No, sorry,
Kevin Bacon wasn't in Footloose.
- What? Of course he was.
- No, he wasn't. You lose.
- Of course he was. He was the star.
- No, you're wrong. Look it up.
I don't have to look it up.
It's common knowledge.
- He was on the cover of...
- No, no, no.
...People magazine when the movie...
- No, no.
- Everyone knows...
...Kevin Bacon was the star of Footloose.
- No, no, no!
- It was a huge movie. He was the lead.
- No, no, no, no!
No, no, no...
Look what the Lynches gave us.
A needlepoint of Chuck Norris
from Walker, Texas Ranger.
You know, they say
Chuck Norris is so tough,
there's no chin under his beard.
- There is only another fist.
- That's ridiculous.
Chuck Norris?
You know, this place may be the upside
to everything that's happened.
The people are kind and generous.
They seem wholesome and moral,
exactly the kind of influence
this family needs.
Lois, we're living in a red state
with a bunch of right-wing nut jobs.
Hey, Chris, check out my belt buckle.
It says, "Everything's bigger in Texas. "
Belts are a great way to express opinions.
This is Channel Five News,
Texas, with Duke Dillon.
Howdy, Texas, I'm Duke Dillon.
At the top of the news tonight,
authorities have called off their pursuit
of a fugitive Rhode Island baby who was
thought to be possessed by the devil.
Oh, thank God.
This turn of events came
after Vatican scientists announced today
that the devil is not the greatest threat
to salvation
due to last week's discovery
of the super devil.
Religion reporter Dallas Houston
has the story.
Thanks, Duke.
Well, let me try to give you a clear picture
of what we're dealing with here.
Here's a photo of the devil,
and here's the super devil.
Now, as you can see,
there are some significant differences.
The super devil is at least 6 inches taller.
He has a flying motorcycle
and a jar of marmalade that we believe
forces you to commit adultery.
Thanks a lot, Dallas.
Looks like we've all got
something new to be afraid of.
Everyone, it's over.
We can go back to Quahog.
Hey, Lois, did you say something?
Oh, just that I think
you're gonna love this cake.
None for me, thanks.
It's gonna go straight to my vagina.
That's what girls worry about, right?
Having big vaginas?
Dad, why aren't you taking the car?
Chris, we're in Texas now.
If I'm not riding a horse,
I'm gonna stick out like a straight guy
in a figure skating competition.
Boo-ya! Triple salchow in your face!
Hey, you want this?
Huh? You want some of this?
Oh, man, look at your rack.
I'd motorboat that.
I'd motorboat the hell out of it.
Right after this layback spin.
Bottle of Jack Daniel's, please.
- Here you go.
- Thanks. What's this?
That's your gun.
Buy some liquor, get a free gun.
Is that, like,
a special you have on now or something?
Nope, Texas state law.
You have a nice day now.
State law?
God, this place officially sucks
worse than the WNBA.
And at the top of the second half,
it's 16 to 9.
Easton leads the scoring with four.
And that's why
she commands $7,000 a year.
These gals sure do make it look difficult.
But is having this minor skill
worth being so unattractive?
That's for the fan to decide.
Yay!
Huh.
That was kind of cool.
Been a long day, Lois. Long day.
Peter, what the hell?
You can't bring that horse into our bed!
Lois, I cannot believe
you would ban the horse from our bed.
He is a graceful, majestic creature
who is a part of this family
and only wants your love and respect.
The horse may have pooped in the bed.
I hereby call this meeting
of the Texas Youth Club to order.
First, I'd like to welcome our
two newcomers, Chris and Meg Griffin.
Wow, this is the coolest club
I've ever been in.
Well, you're not quite in the club yet.
- You got to pass the initiation.
- What do we have to do?
You got to sneak onto the Crawford Ranch
and steal a pair of
George Bush's underwear.
And then bring it back here,
so we can bask in its Bushy goodness.
Boy, that's even kinkier than the porn
they make for senior citizens.
Can I help you, Edward?
Yeah, I'm here for the early bird special.
- Are those new slacks?
- What's that now?
- I got these on special at Caldor.
- Who drove you there?
- My nephew.
Oh!
That was nice of him.
I forgot why I came over.
Are those new slacks?
What is this?
What the hell are we doing here?
Welcome to your first
toddler pageant, Stewie.
It's what you do when you're in Texas.
Oh, lovely. A first-class ticket to a
semen-covered death in the basement.
Why don't you meet the other contestants
while I go register you?
Hello, I'm Stephanie Griffin.
- Hi, Stephanie.
- What's your talent?
I sing, I do gymnastics, and I can play
seven instruments at the same time.
You could be a threat to me. Chuck.
There it is. The Crawford Ranch.
I can't believe we're actually doing this.
What a bonding adventure
for the two of us.
Settle down, Meg. Okay, I see
old man Cheney guarding the place.
18% approval ratings.
I'll give you 18% of my foot in your ass.
I'd like you to meet
my daughter's husband, Michael.
Wow, look how organized he is.
He's already got his sugar cut up into neat
little lines for his breakfast tomorrow.
And a razor blade to shave.
Wow, look at this.
I can't believe Mrs. Bush kept
all these Planned Parenthood receipts.
Holy cow!
She's been scraped more times
than a fisherman's knuckle.
Hey! What are you kids doing here?
You tell Javier to back off.
I'll have his money by next week.
- What?
- Never mind.
Hey, you guys wanna see something?
Grab a beer and follow me.
See this car?
I restored it myself this summer.
I was here for 12 weeks.
I had to do something.
But along the way,
I learned about honesty, integrity
and cold-filtered Miller Genuine Draft.
That's an adult beverage right there.
You understand
what I'm trying to say to you?
Yes, but I have just one question.
Can I borrow your underpants
for 10 minutes?
Hello? Oh, hi, Jillian.
Brian, I'm reading TV Guide.
Can you explain how these
"cheers" and "jeers" work again?
Well, the "cheers" is when they generally
approve of something on television,
and "jeers" is when
they find some sort of fault with it.
See, yeah, I'm not quite...
We can't do this over the phone.
You're gonna have to come over.
I can't come over. We're still on the run,
because the town thinks
Stewie's possessed.
No, they don't. Didn't you hear?
They stopped chasing you weeks ago.
- What? I have to go.
- Wait, wait, I have another question.
How do I know if I'm Jewish?
- Are you Jewish?
- No.
- There you go, sport.
- Thank you.
Hey, guys, thanks so much
for inviting me out today.
I'm psyched to brand my first cow.
Here you are, Peter.
All fired up and ready to go.
Yes! Yes! Hang on a second.
Man, Texas is great. Back where I'm from,
a retarded guy
could never have this much fun.
- What'd you just say?
- What? Technically, I'm retarded.
Fellas, fellas, can't we talk this over?
Talking is for terrorists and blacks.
In Texas, we execute the retarded!
Oh, my God. So, this is how it ends?
I always thought I'd die having to
sit through the Canadian Film Festival.
I don't wish to cause you any harm,
and I won't. The end.
- Horsey, you saved my life.
- No problem, Peter.
- Glad to help out.
- Wow, Gilbert Gottfried.
- That's right!
- Awesome.
Now, the final contestant for
our talent portion of the competition,
- Stephanie Griffin.
- Thank you, thank you.
Hey, what's the deal
with Chunky bars, huh?
Chocolate with raisins in it.
Yeah, that's what kids want
with their chocolate, fruit.
Wow, that bit's killing.
Hey, Lois, great news.
We can go back to Quahog.
Yeah, I know, Brian.
We're about to see if Stewie won.
Wait a minute, you know?
How long have you known?
- A few weeks. Who cares?
- Wait a minute. You...
You've known for weeks and you've been
lying about having to stay here?
Brian, don't you see?
This is a wholesome community
with real values.
And our first runner-up is...
Miss Dixie-Ann Thomas,
which means that Miss Stephanie Griffin
is our new Little Miss Texas!
Oh! Oh, my God!
Oh, I never expected this!
Oh, I'm so, so honored!
- Hey! That's not a girl!
- It's Enrico Palazzo!
No, it's not!
It's one of them queerosexuals!
Get him!
Quick, get on!
- Thank you for all your help.
- My pleasure, Peter.
- Any time.
- Oh, fantastic.
- Hey, do you still do stand-up?
- I do. I'm still touring.
- Oh, wow, can we get tickets?
- Absolutely.
- I'm in Atlanta next week.
- Great. Oh, well, this will be fun.
It is so good to be home.
You know, I wanted us to live in a place
with real family values.
But values don't come from where you live
or who your friends are.
They come from inside,
from your own beliefs.
I agree, Lois. Like for instance,
if you're watching a TV show
and you decide to take your values
from that, you're an idiot.
Maybe you should take responsibility
for what values your kids are getting.
Maybe you shouldn't be letting your kids
watch certain shows in the first place
if you have such a big problem with them,
instead of blaming the shows themselves.
Yeah.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru